{
    "subject": "resource/Zaman_(newspaper)",
    "predicate": "property/headquarters",
    "object": "A. Taner K\u0131\u015flal\u0131 Cad. No:6",
    "human_readable": "The headquarters of Zaman newspaper is located at A. Taner K\u0131\u015flal\u0131 Cad. No:6.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9863481521606445,
            "question": "At what number on A. Taner K\u0131\u015flal\u0131 Cad. is Zaman newspaper's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9801595211029053,
            "question": "Where is the headquarters of Zaman newspaper located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9705304503440857,
            "question": "On which street is the headquarters of Zaman newspaper situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9563466310501099,
            "question": "Zaman newspaper's headquarters is located on which street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.942055881023407,
            "question": "What is the full address of Zaman newspaper's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9333087801933289,
            "question": "What is the physical location of Zaman newspaper's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9310534596443176,
            "question": "What is the street address of Zaman newspaper's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8882524967193604,
            "question": "Can you provide the house number of Zaman newspaper's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8108842968940735,
            "question": "Where can you find the main offices of Zaman newspaper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5917708277702332,
            "question": "Give me the address of Zaman newspaper's main office."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The headquarters of Zaman newspaper is located at A. Taner K\u0131\u015flal\u0131 Cad. No:6.",
            "html": "dbpedia_904_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find the main offices of Zaman newspaper?",
            "html": "dbpedia_904_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide the house number of Zaman newspaper's headquarters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_904_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the street address of Zaman newspaper's headquarters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_904_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_904_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_904_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_904_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_904_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_904_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_904_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_904_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_904_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_904_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_904_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states that the headquarters of the Zaman newspaper is located at \"Fevzi Cakmak Mah.  A. Taner Kislali Cad.  No:6 34194 Bahcelievler, Istanbul\" which matches your triple."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the required format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that the headquarters of Zaman newspaper is located at A. Taner K\u0131\u015flal\u0131 Cad. No:6, as stated in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_904/re-ranker-msmarco/4.txt:\n\n\"Zaman Newspaper\nInfobox Newspaper\nname = Zaman Newspaper\ncaption = The front page with the SND Award of Excellence\ntype = Daily newspaper\nformat = Berliner\nfoundation = 1986\nowners = Feza Inc.\nheadquarters = Fevzi Cakmak Mah.  A. Taner Kislali Cad.  No:6 34194 Bahcelievler, Istanbul TURKEY\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context information clearly states that the \"Zaman\" newspaper's headquarters is located at \"Fevzi Cakmak Mah. A. Taner Kislali Cad. No:6, 34194 Bahcelievler, Istanbul, TURKEY\". This supports the statement that the headquarters of Zaman newspaper is located at A. Taner K\u0131\u015flal\u0131 Cad. No:6."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}